sonepar.fr 2005-09-08

# SONEPAR - Privacy Policy

1/a Sonepar is committed to preserving the confidentiality of any information provided on line. All personal information that an Internet user transmits to Sonepar through the services of the site is subject to French legislation (Loi n° 78-17 Informatique et Libertés du 06 janvier 1 978). This legislation allows Internet users to access, rectify and delete any personal information by submitting a written notice the following address:

1/b Sonepar does not share with third parties any personal information you provide without first obtaining your informed consent.

1/c Sonepar strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Sonepar intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Statement even when we transfer your information from your country to countries that may not require the same level of protection for your information.

 _2°) Information automatically collected _

Sonepar automatically collects and temporarily stores the following information about your computer and your visit:

· the domain and host from which you access the Internet  
· the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to the Sonepar site, if applicable  
· the date and time you arrived at our site and how long you spent on the site and which pages you visited  
· your internet protocol (IP) address  
· your computer's operating system and browser software.

The information above is not linked to your personal identity.

 _3°) Cookies_

 _3/a Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to maintain a virtual session. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized._

3/b The use of cookies on our web site is limited to carrying out this specific function.

3/c We link to the sites of some of our partners if we think their business may be of interest to you. Please be aware that even though we try to choose partners who adhere to similar privacy standards and practices, we cannot control their use of cookies in relation to these links. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site through these links and to read the privacy policies of all sites you visit.

 _4°) Security_

Appropriate safeguards are implemented to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of Personnally-Indentifiable Information about our partners or customers and prospects.

 _5°) Changes to our Privacy Policy_

From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post these changes on this page so that our customers are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share information with others.
